Wyatt from Castle Island here and on today's episode of on the brink stable coin five series
I was joined by Alex Cutler founder of airdrome airdrome is a leading decentralized trading protocol
Operating on Coinbase's native base blockchain. I hope you enjoy our conversation
Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners at Castle Island Ventures
All these expressed by them or the guests on this podcast are solely their opinions and do not reflect the opinions of Castle Island Ventures
Guess the most may maintain positions in the assets discussed in this podcast
You should not treat any opinion expressed by anyone on this podcast as a specific inducement to make a particular investment or
Follow a particular strategy, but only as an expression of their personal opinion. This podcast is for informational purposes only
Brought down by bad mortgage investments Lehman, which has 25,000 employees will be liquidated the federal government loans American International Group
85 billion dollars
This is a different kind of market and the Fed is asleep
The federal government is stepping it to stabilize Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac the two mortgage giants that have been threatened by the housing
Crisis the bank of England has pumped 75 billion pounds more to Britain's ailing economy with a new round of cost to do these
In a print a couple trillion dollars and all of a sudden people start to worry so out of this worry
We have something called the Bitcoin Bitcoin
Alex Cutler co-founder of airdrome finance
Thank you for joining the podcast today excited to have you if it works
Would love to kick off with a quick background and hear about your story and journey to crypto
Thanks so much for having me very excited to be here
I think my journey like a lot of folks in crypto was pretty
Twisty turning very much not a direct path. I started my career working in politics and campaigns
Got pretty burned out on that win and spend some time working in big tech
Decided I needed to mix it up and spend some time in the agency and consulting world and
I actually think it's pretty interesting because I was like many people
Hold up in the pandemic decided to build a gaming PC
I had friends who were very much into crypto and defy at that point
Encouraging me to get involved. So I decided I would just start mining some Bitcoin with the PC
And then I took the Bitcoin and I was like wow
I made something out of seemingly nothing and what can I do with this and brought it on to an exchange
Then brought it on chain
started yield farming
started playing around with all these different protocols and I think once you have a taste of
the way in which this
Industry creates so much freedom of opportunity and you can contribute in ways and be rewarded
I was totally hooked. So I ended up quitting my job
Didn't really have a plan other than playing around on chain
I didn't know what I was going to do. But one thing led to another
I met some other very very smart guys and became a
Accidental founder in the space. I love that story
I relate to some degree because I'd studied political science in college and that was a lot of my interest area and had a similar
Experience that playing around on chain for me was very freeing in a way to be in a free financial system
When you know about all the entanglement of traditional financial governance, I found that to be immediately a pretty powerful thing
Yeah, it was weird
There's an old Steve jobs line about how you can only connect the dots going backwards and in a strange way the combination of
politics
Technology of getting exposure to the agency and consulting world to all these different business models
In some ways was the perfect pedigree to come into this on-chain world because all of this matters
models matter
incentives matter
Community and there are certainly politics to all of this matter and obviously technology matters
So this ended up being a perfect blend of experience
I feel like diving into a space that is still so like raw and unshaped with all those different pieces
And how did you go from being curious on chain to being someone at the forefront of building crypto products?
the thing that I
Really really appreciate about the space is that if you just show up and you start
Contributing if you just show up and start adding value and that could be just through on-chain actions, of course
You can contribute value to protocols to projects and never even have a public-facing persona
You could just be a wallet participating
But if you do have a public persona you can participate in all sorts of ways
Initially, I just started as I was learning things
I would write threads about the project or protocol I was learning about and that was largely an exercise and
Learning for me in the sense of you only know you understand something if you can relate it back and have people tell you
Yep, that is correct. You've understood it correctly
So I started writing these threads about things that I was interested in and you know
I think my initial gateway to the ecosystem is the first project. I was very passionate about was Curve and
the very very interesting model that Mitch had built there and
writing threads about that and the writing threads about
Solidly, which was Andre Crone's big project and before I knew it somebody who was part of a
Dow said hey, man, could you come help us?
And then I start helping a little more on the writing thread side and then it's well now
There's five more things that need to be done. Let me help on those things. So I start helping
I start contributing more and there are just few spaces where absent a pedigree
job application
All the things that keep people boxed in or on particular lines
Don't exist here if you just show up and you start kicking down doors start adding value
Experiences like mine are definitely on the table because that now that I got pulled into just because I was writing some interesting threads
that now is the now that had the idea initially a
velodrome and that of course evolved into
airdrome and
It was just a bunch of in the beginning and on
Discord people none of us knew who each other were we didn't know each other's work backgrounds ages
We didn't know where anybody lived in the world
It was just an alignment of interests and then us collectively seeing an opportunity and organizing dense that opportunity
You make a great point the free system of finance creates also a free market for human capital
If I think Callan Lee should do something and I'm a major Callan Lee user
I can't just go contribute readily you typically can't do so outside of your day job
I think it's a very powerful part of crypto
Is that something that you guys have implemented and is that something that grounded your origin story with airdrome?
It's actually at the core of our model, which I'm sure we can get into a bit more in time
But the economics of our model are such that every single
Participant in the system is on equal footing. So
We as a team we don't have any privileged access to any of the revenue that the protocol generates
We have to do the same thing anybody does each week if we want sort of access
we have to basically participate we have to have value and
That is no different than a venture fund who comes in and locks up the token
They have the same access to the revenue of producers
They have to contribute value in the exact same way and that's the same exact thing that any degen or user does
If you're just a passionate person who goes out locks some tokens and is participating each week
You are on equal footing with the team here on equal footing with point-based ventures
You're on equal footing with somebody who's taken millions of the coins and locked them up and somebody who's locked up a few and
Your incentives are now aligned
Organically with those of the protocol what you contribute into it is rewarded and incentivized the same way as
The team and I think that is the power of the model to happen many cases
But there's one guy I think about a lot who just so happened to
At one of the lows in the market
he locked up a ton of arrow because he was interested in the protocol and
In locking up that arrow and voting each week and earning back the rewards
Basically the value the protocol is generating
He was able to take time off of work and what he did with this time off of work
It was just starting writing really deep research threads on
Aero drone and on the decks market plays on the industry generally and these are some of the best
Threads ever so and they've been massively impactful and it was just we didn't have to hire him
We didn't have to compromise his independence
We didn't have to really do anything
His incentive alignment was created organically through this economic system
And I think that is absolutely what makes it so powerful and it is it is embedded entirely into the model where
Those who contribute the most are basically rewarded the most and the downstream effects of that are very powerful
Can you speak a bit more to that economic incentive structure model for those who might be less familiar?
So I guess I'll take a step back and talk about dex's generally and the incentive structures there and the different groups that they are balancing
So a dex you'd say has three primary stakeholder groups
there are traders and
Traders fundamentally just want the best execution on their trades
They will trade on any dex as long as that dex has the tokens that they want to trade and that dex is giving them the best execution
So that's one group you are controlling for who provides the liquidity for that
That is liquidity providers. Those are the people coming in who are putting up two sides of any given trade
so your bitcoin and your
USDC so they create the pool through it all those trades will go through
But they're taking on risk in doing this the idea of impermanent loss that the values of those change
That can certainly be something that they're basically taking some risk on so you need to give them the best rewards
So we're trying to give traders the best execution
We're going to do that by giving liquidity providers the best rewards
And then that third group is basically token holders dex's do need tokens. This is very important
We know that because if you go back in the history
We've seen that you can take a dex with no token a dex with a token
And within a week the dex with the token who can basically have a little bit of extra value
Can take half of the whole liquidity from the dex without the token
So token holders are an important part of it
And token holders are basically going to be interested in how much reward can I have for holding the token?
And they need to be there to optimize the dex to ensure that the value is flowing to the right liquidity providers
So basically by aligning the incentives between these three groups of
traders liquidity providers and token holders
You end up with an economic model that is very very powerful
One of the big differences is if you go back and we call this the dex trilemma
Uniswap, which was really the first pioneer here
It solved it between two parties and solved it between traders and liquidity providers
But it was a bit tapped because it was only exchanging fees and liquidity between these two parties
Curve was the next big innovation in the sense of we're going to add in a token to ensure you can incentivize
liquidity providers beyond just the fee capture
And there's a lot of other reasons tokens are useful in this context too
But you know, we're going to send only half of the fees to the token and half to liquidity providers
So in our model basically the big breakthrough is that you want to give
100% of the revenue to the token and give the token basically to liquidity providers
And that is the ultimate state of this dex trilemma. All three parties see their interests aligned
Everyone gets the best version of whatever that activity is that they are doing and that leads to just a much more efficient model
And trading in cryptos gravitated a lot in this sense today you've centralized exchanges that are listing assets
they wouldn't have historically in the past and
I think you and I are both aligned that that incentive structure and model has a lot of unlocks, but in 2025
for skeptics
Why is dex trading necessary and why are dex is structurally necessary in crypto when you have all this sex trading at the same time?
And you'll probably have traditional brokerages facilitating the trading of crypto assets as well
I think you just cannot beat open permissionless markets
And this is actually a trend we're seeing right now. Think about what every centralized exchange has to go through to get new
tokens launched on their platforms trading on their platforms
They need to go through an incredible amount of due diligence overhead. This is legal due diligence
This is regulatory due diligence. This is a degree of due diligence on the teams on the token supplies
This is engineering work to get it all plugged in. This is comms and marketing work
This is needing to ensure that you are attracting market makers to actually ensure that these markets on the centralized exchanges
Will bootstrap effectively
This is why the centralized exchanges are these very large entities because this is all
Very time-intensive very expensive work and it's even at its fastest state pretty slow
If you think about
All of that and you think about the fact that on chain you can spin up these markets
Maybe even a way to think about it is on the centralized exchange. You're spinning them up
Decentralized exchange is everyone's spinning them up. They're being spun up all the time in real time
And we've seen this not only massive expansion and the number of tokens
But also even the life cycles of tokens collapsing
There's just no way a centralized exchange is going to be able to
Through their traditional process keep up with the
On-chain economy in the way in which all this new activity all these new tokens can just be organically sort of spun up
And I think the trend that you're actually seeing which is very interesting is that
centralized exchanges are getting increasingly interested in actually
integrating with dex pools on chain pools and
Surfacing those to their customers because in the end of your trading on point base or finance or whatever
You don't really care how they get you access to the tokens
You're just going to care that when you go to trade the tokens there
And if it launched yesterday if the president of the united states is launching a coin
And it is popping off and you go to by an answer you go to
Coinbase and it's not there to trade it means you're not going to trade there
And that's a loss for you as the customer and that's a loss for them as an exchange business
If they can surface to their customers everything that's happening on chain while passing off the responsibility
Of all that due diligence of building the markets to that on-chain infrastructure
I think it's the best of both worlds where they're going to be able to service their customers all those things
They're going to be able to spin up in real time
And by the way because we are talking about the ways in which we're going to expand asset classes
The things that are tokenized on chain
There are also just going to be things that I think centralized exchanges are just not going to be interested in taking on the risk of
Integrating directly into their products, but they will be able to say okay
Well, we're just giving our users access to something that's happening on chain wash their hands of it
It's much much easier. So finances already started doing this
Brian Armstrong he said publicly that they are beginning to integrate d-fi
There's a great new product on coinbase that allows you to borrow against your bitcoin as a coinbase user
You probably wouldn't even know that that is all happening via d-fi protocols on base
And I expect that we'll see more dex integrations in centralized exchanges because of the things that we're describing here
I think you make excellent points
I also think the visibility into the pools is powerful because as I think we both know that there are some
Incredible antics that happen when it comes to some of the tokens that list on centralized exchanges
Where you can't see what's happening in the background and you're really just presented with market cap valuation
And do you want to buy this token?
That's one of the reasons I think people loved dex screener actually was because it made it so obvious to see
These transactions you can see what looks like a bot you can see what looks like a real transaction
And you really don't have that especially today with these centralized exchanges
Yeah, watching the order books on centralized exchanges, especially in tokens with relatively limited liquidity on them
there's a game being played and the transparency
That on chain pools give you is just not going to be rivaled at all by centralized order books and things like that
Yeah, it makes you question systems of traditional trading when you have this new alternative of a transparent trading system
Think about even just the market making side of this
If you are going to go and get listed on
centralized exchange the first question they're going to ask you is do you have a market maker?
Is somebody going to be able to come in and ensure that there is some degree of sufficient liquidity on those books so that our customers
When they come to trade we'll be able to trade is there going to be somebody who's going to be actively arbitraging
these between the on chain pools and the pools on our exchange and
When you're talking about pools on chain, you don't need to hire anybody to make those markets
You just align the incentives such that everybody from somebody who's a very very professional
Liquidity provider or market maker they're going to show up and do it as long as they're properly incentivized to do it
But you haven't had to have any centralized interaction with them
And then you can also just have average joe people and this is what I was saying when I first got in
One of the early things I did was started to provide liquidity because I had just two tokens
And I saw a reward if I put these two tokens together
So even as the biggest newbie
I had access to something and was able to help provide liquidity in the same way that the centralized parties previously were required to do it
And that's the power of access and transparency that the on chain world gives you
You observe a lot of these trading systems, obviously
What assets are you seeing activity in or where do you think we are in the life cycle of assets people want to trade and defy?
I think we're at a very interesting point
The big thing that has happened is that the regulatory landscape in the united states has changed significantly
And this has a bunch of downstream
Implications people are thinking about how they're designing tokens differently
I think one of the big issues in our industry is the fact that 90
Of tokens in my opinion are functionally mean coins. You can say it's a governance coin
You can say it's a utility coin
But if that governance or utility isn't enforced by on chain like immutable mechanisms
It's functionally a mean coin if there's no direct value flow in the form of incentives or other things for participation
It's functionally a mean coin
So I think one thing that I'm very very interested in and we've heard this a lot from
Funds is that they are functionally done playing games with these tokens that don't actually do anything
That don't actually have any of fundamentals surrounding them
So I think we'll see an explosion of more tokens with real
Actual utility these are things that do things that there are fundamental factors associated to these they can actually be used
And I think that is very exciting because tokens should be one of the most powerful tools
That we have for like disintermediating
businesses organizations products and things like that
And when you just intermediate things there's more value for the common
So number one is I think just more useful interesting tokens
And we've been seeing a ton of new stuff launching on base that would fit that category
The second thing is that I think we will continue to see a course of vast majority of trading happen around those top 10 assets
And I think what's exciting for us is that we expect far more of that trading activity to happen on base
To consolidate around a few networks because when you're trading these like we've talked about fundamentally you care about execution
And ideally you want to be able to trade between all of them in the same place
So we worked with the Coinbase team to basically make base the best place to trade bitcoin on chain
And this end is like multi year incumbency because on chain the best place to trade bitcoin for so long had been on a theory main net
because that's where all the liquidity was on uniswap and
using WBTC and it took two weeks for base and airdrome to basically make the top venue for trading bitcoin on chain
base and airdrome and I think you could do that for the top 10 trading assets
And then traders increasingly have no reason to leave that ecosystem because if they want to
Move between whichever major is hot in size and the best place to do it is all on base
They're not going to need to go bridge anywhere else
All the major market makers will just be harbing between Coinbase and those which creates even more fees and economic activity
So I think we'll see even more trading around the majors
Especially if we see more things get ETFs and we see flows into it
But there are a few other things that I would highlight one is FX FX is trillion dollar market
and FX is something where you're not just talking about
The speculators the people who are trading currency for some degree of edge. You're talking about payments processors worldwide
And payments processing is something that as of right now
The margins on it at times are just absolutely offensive if you are taking a trip to europe
it's an american and you're going to an atm
Or buying something you're paying percentages on that transaction just to take your dollars into europe's
Even the best payments platform like wise
It's a pretty healthy take on that and right now today on base
You can go from us dollars to euros at a better rate than any institution in trafi and fintech can provide you
And we've onboarded. I think another 10 new global stables
The goal of the base team is to have a stable representation of every major on-chain currency by the end of year
And to onboard those payments providers because we know we can give them better execution
Not in the future not hypothetically. We can do that today
And I think that's going to be another very very powerful
Expansion of what people are trading or using and then the last piece
I think is we've talked about for a long time on-chain markets are just better markets
They're always on the settlement is instant and I think there is no reason why we shouldn't see every asset type
So tokenized equities derivatives real world assets on-chain and the compounding effect of all of this
Top 10 digital assets new emergent digital assets
Every single global currency stablecoin and a whole bunch of real world assets and it's all happening in one place
What does this add up to this adds up to the single best marketplace in the world for traders of assets
Speculators of assets and that's what we're very very excited about and I think that's part of why we have been
So bullish on base and coin bases because I think they
Share that vision and they believe it's in their interest to cultivate the world's best market on base
I think you're spot on on both of those two major points
Shout out coin base has done an incredible job in creating a seamless bitcoin experience off the bitcoin main chain
Which I think is very necessary in crypto
I really want to zoom in on the on-chain fx piece because it's something we're very interested in
I think it could be a killer use case of crypto beyond stablecoins being completely honest or called a step two
I've always thought just really deep d5 pools of different fiat currencies or fiat back stablecoins is already an incredible use case
We've seen a fantastic batch of innovation around usd stablecoins settlement systems
That sit on top on on and off ramping infrastructure
From my perspective the limiting factor for these on-chain fx systems is a lack of liquidity for these other
currency stablecoins and
A lack of accompanying infrastructure on the orchestration and on an off-ramp side
How are you guys looking at that or trying to bridge that gap as you build out this initiative?
This is where it's a great
1-2 punch
Collaboration I think between us and the coin base team
So we have the ability very very easily to scale up liquidity on any type of asset
And this is one of the superpowers of the metadex model. That's what we call velodrome heredrome. They're metadexes
they are probably the best liquidity bootstrapping systems in define and the example that is the
cbbtc the coin base bitcoin product that I mentioned
Multiple years of incumbency ended because we were able to bootstrap in a matter of weeks enough liquidity to make base the on-chain hub
So we have the ability to bootstrap basically infinite amounts of liquidity on these global fx pairs
And if you think about people looping those and to borrow lend protocols and things like that
liquidity can scale up very very quick and the market rate
LP and aprs on these types of pairs would be way lower than what people demand on most tokens
So that's one side of it and we can nudge and dial that up as we see demand
But where is the demand coming from and how are we solving these other problems like onboarding offboarding and things like that?
That is where the base team and coin base team is very very focused
So they are not just trying to onboard good representations of global currencies
But they are trying to onboard the ecosystems around it
So they are working with local payments providers in these countries
They are working with on ramps off ramps in these countries to ensure that basically the full stack
Of usage comes in but really in our mind because we know the activities there
People have entire businesses right now and they're paying way more than they should be paying to go between these
To settle between these different assets
Just to do the work that they do and provide their customers the things that their customers need
If you can onboard just a few of these big players
We're talking about organic non-toxic flows between these assets that are always on and they're not subject to market volatility
sufficient to bootstrap a lot more fees and a lot more activity
And if they come in and they say hey
Well, we need to be routing another 2 million a day between these pools, but the liquidity isn't sufficient
But they tell us those flows are going to come we as a voter
We could just vote more emissions to bootstrap more liquidity so that they can start building those flows
And I do think that has been what's missing
Somebody who is very focused on capable of building the on-chain liquidity
And then somebody who's trying to bring all of the
Ecosystem around that at the same time to come tap into that liquidity
And if you can do those two things, we know the product does matter
I think it would very quickly flywheel where more volume means more fees means more tvl
It really bootstrapping and now it's actually deep enough that those FX speculators might actually want to start coming on chain
And making those markets on chain as well. So, yeah, I think that's the secret sauce is
We've had people building pockets of these things
But we haven't had full sides of it coming together in one place to execute
It seems very lucrative for anyone with the assets
personally
We're seeing a ton of volume from us to mexico using stablecoins in the middle
But you can't do it in fashion that goes through an mxn stablecoin because there's really no liquidity behind any of these
mxn stablecoins
I had etherfuse on the podcast recently who are trying to do it and I hope they'll be successful
But still small markets there. Do you think there will be a
Traditional finance or mainstream actor that moves into this opportunity and then we'll get this inflection point
I think of like a Susquehanna or someone like that who could come in and really move the scale of the liquidity in these markets
And then all of a sudden we have robust on chain mxn
Euros etc or what does the zero to one moment look like here?
The answer to the question is absolutely
And we've talked to I think so many
Institutions who are starting to go down this path regulatory clarity is going to help a lot around the stable bill
But it seems like the major major players understand the value prop now. They're moving. They're very slow
Apparatuses they're doing their exploration
So I think there will be that big moment where somebody very very large comes in
But in the meantime, I think the growth is still going to be incredible
Just in onboarding almost all the smaller fish in relative terms
And that's going to basically create the proof points to the major players that this is real
This is useful because there are now businesses putting more and more flows through these and again non-toxic flows
This is real organic usage
And if they continue to see that drip drip drip
Someone's going to come in and win because it's a market. It's a market to be one
We continue to see more of these consumer facing apps with crypto in the background. We have the d5 mullet
It's almost like the stablecoin mullet now
Do you hope that eventually
Aerodrome becomes a venue that people interact with less directly and you become the liquidity venue underpinning
FX and underpinning major asset trading. Do you hope to retain a sizable front-end audience?
Or where do you guys hope to sit on the spectrum?
I think about this as like an 80-20 thing
There's always going to be a need for some degree of a front-end
Especially in the way in which we democratize access to all of these things. We said liquidity providers
Blockers of the tokens voting to direct emissions and certainly two degree traders
But a dex is just fundamentally infrastructure. It's essential infrastructure for an on-chain economy
And most of the people who will interact with our infrastructure will have no idea that they are interacting with their infrastructure
They will just be using products like a payments platform
Like a social network with an on-chain economy behind it
They will just be getting exposure to major digital assets and they will have no idea how they did it
Again going back to the trilemma. They're just going to care about the best execution the best access to them
So I do think and this has been a big difference between us and say uniswap because I think uniswap at some point
Decided that hey, we want to be the front-end
We want to be the entry point and we're going to put a lot of time and focus into being the front-end
And the entry point to this ecosystem
And I think the issue with that is just that think about who else wants to be the front-end
Coinbase wants to be the front-end
Metamask lots of people want to be the front-end
Robin probably wants to be the front-end and these are consumer
Application building companies. They've got billions of dollars not in their own token
They've got billions of real dollars to invest in winning this fight. So why would a crypto company say
I'm going to go kick coinbase's ass here. I'm going to beat Robin hood versus you focus on
Ensuring that you will be the deepest most liquid source of these things
And no matter who builds the front-end they have to use your liquidity
So I think that is our vision and the other thing about the front-end thing is let me just look at the explosion of ai agents
Coinbase Robin hood and seeing every major stock exchange is going to start getting into digital assets
They're all going to be competing to be the front-end of this ecosystem
But you also have crazy new emergent things like natural language ai interfaces that might disrupt all of these
So why go compete over there? Why not just let them fight it out and ensure that whenever they are doing a swap
If they want to deliver to their customers the best execution, they're going to have to use our rails
So yeah, that is a hundred percent our focus. We know we'll win if we always have the
Deepest liquidity in the active tick. So we should invest all of our R&D our effort our economics aligned around that
Let's not go waste a bunch of time and money trying to be a better front-end than some amazing front-ends
From that perspective
Do you look at anyone who can quickly catalyze large-scale liquidity as potential competition?
Is that what keeps you up at night?
Or do you look at players of that regard who might be again large asset managers large bank type institutions?
Are they just in a different neck of the woods?
If somebody were to genuinely want to compete with us for this liquidity advantage
the interesting thing about the dex trilemma is just that it's fixed
And because we reward our LPs with our token and because we generate all this revenue
And we send all of it out to the token as incentives
You can't offer them more than 100 of the productive value of the dex
There's no greater value problem. You can offer liquidity providers than 100 of the productive value and not just today
But in the future
So we do certainly think about it a lot and we do think about other ways
In which we can send even more value back to that token as incentives
So that the rewards for again that active tick liquidity are even higher
But fundamentally because we went all the way out in this fixed conditions
There is nothing anybody could do that would be giving people more than 100 of the value
So you'd have to do something basically like us and then somebody would have to look at it and say well
Why is this other person deliver 100 of the productive value back going to beat the network effects of the other team?
That's doing this and already has the liquidity as people building on it and all this stuff
So that's what gives us comfort is we took a big risk. I think betting that way
We didn't raise any money. We didn't sell any tokens
We didn't even give team liquid vesting allocations of our tokens
We just bet on the token is useful and we will bet our lives on the token being useful
And that bet's paid off
But there's really nothing in the dex trilemma that you can do that is more than giving 100 of the current and future capitalized value
You're giving anyone who contributes regardless of who they are the best value proposition inherently
And that's what we reward our liquidity providers with is the token that represents that
To close out. I wanted to ask you what keeps you up at night operating in the spaces you do in the industry
I think for a long time, especially for me coming into the industry when I did and velodrome launching in 2022
The biggest thing that kept us up at night was just the legal and regulatory overhead. Don't get me wrong
I think that there is just a ton of nasty shit in this industry
And I think we need rules and I think we need people enforcing those rules
And I am hopeful that we'll see real sensible
Legislation that doesn't treat this industry as the same as a million other industries that have come before that treats it as a new
emergent technology
But the scariest part of building was that we did everything right or at least as insofar as we could
Determine what was right? What was legal?
You could ask a hundred lawyers the same question and they say well
We think you should do this
But we all know if there's no overzealous regulators going to show up tomorrow and say based on the 1910 whatever act
We actually think this thing is not legal and we're going to ruin your life
So the biggest thing that's kept me up at night has definitely diminished a lot post election
And that I think is a very good thing. I think the other things that keep me up
Right now it's macro just because hey guys, we can believe in the vision of the space
We can believe that we're inevitable
But unfortunately we're still furthest out on the risk curve and if every major asset class
It's going to get the shit kicked out of it. We're going to feel that even more
But other than those two things
I think just the vision of hey what this technology allows us to do is to build
institutional level products and services
free of intermediaries
It allows us to do that in a way that creates all this surplus value that can be returned to the commons
In the end the history of technology is that the best product wins
I have no
fear that
This industry the technology the things that we were building will win
It's just all of the roller coaster of that journey to that mass adoption place
That's probably a bit painful
Lots to be excited about but to your point we are still tethered to the platform risk of humanity
Yes, unfortunately
Well, alex. Thank you for joining really enjoyed our conversation. Hope to have you back sometime soon
Likewise. Thank you so much for having me
Thanks for listening to another episode of on the brink with castle island to find out more about castle island visit castle island dot vc
To listen to all of our podcast episodes, please go to on the brink dash podcast dot com
Or just click on the tab in our website. Thanks for listening